Larry Burrows Wished For It All... Until All That He Wished For Came True!
Mr. Destiny is a fantasy, comedy, science fiction film directed by James Orr.
Larry Burrows is unhappy and feels powerless over his life.
He believes his entire life could have turned out differently had he
not missed that shot in a baseball game when was a kid.
One night he meets this mysterious man, who could change his fate by
offering him that alternative life he always dreamed of.
But as Burrows embarks on this journey of self discovery he realises
that even this new life has its problems and drawbacks..
Larry Burrows, played by Jim Belushi.
Ellen Burrows, played by Linda Hamilton.
Mike, played by Michael Caine.
Clip Metzler, played by Jon Lovitz.
Niles Pender, played by Hart Bochner.
Leo Hansen, played by Bill McCutcheon.
Destiny is a 1990 American fantasy comedy film directed by James Orr, and starring Jim
Belushi, Linda Hamilton, Michael Caine, Jon Lovitz, Courteney Cox, Jay O.
Sanders and Rene Russo.
It is heavily inspired by the 1946 film It's a Wonderful Life.
In the film, a man in his 30s blames most of his life's problems on
his failure in a baseball game during his adolescence.
His guardian angel grants him the wish to see that failure corrected.
The man is transported to an alternative reality where he has had a
more successful career and a more powerful position.
The price is that he has lost his loved ones from his
previous life and has multiple new enemies.
The film explores themes of wish, aggressive, candid, absurd, hilarious.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.